Aren't you earning enough?
Do really need money that badly?
I'll use it to pay off our debts.
Once that's done,
I can finally do what I've always wanted.
You know, I know a producer
who's planning to produce an indie film.
I think you're fit for the lead role.
No! Wait!
-Wait, just a second.
-Patricia!
Hey! What are you doing to my daughter?
Do you think I don't tell myself that?
I'm stupid! I'm so stupid!
I'm such an idiot!
Hey.
-Are you okay?
-Oh.
Yes. It's nothing. Just a sprain.
That was intense.
You were like an action star back there.
That's what all that coffee does to you.
You needed help, Patricia.
Thanks.
Are you okay?
You're still joking around.
Yes.
I'm over it now.
Besides, I talked to the police.
They're taking them to the station.
I'm not asking what happened.
I'm asking how you're feeling.
Alive and kicking.
You don't have to pretend you're strong
all the time, Patricia.
It's okay.
It's okay to let it all out.
I can handle it.
I'll get through this.
There's nothing I can't handle.
Mm.
I'm right here, okay?
Anytime.
And don't worry.
I won't tell anyone
at the office you cried.
Don't worry.
I'll get through this.
I'm not planning to stay down for long.
If I let everything
that's happened in my life get to me…
you might not be able
to talk to me anymore.
Oh, hello, Sis!
Sis?
Are you okay? You look pale.
Oh, dear.
I'm glad you're home.
Did something happen?
I'm just tired, Dad.
Are you sure?
The nerve of those people!
Why, Mom? What happened?
I got fired from the municipal office.
What?
They accused me of taking bribes.
That's not right.
Let's file a complaint.
But, Mom…
Were you really taking bribes?
April, watch your mouth.
That's not the point.
The point is, I just got fired.
What do we do now?
Patricia, get me some water.
Yes, Mom.
Dear…
What are we going to do now?
Uh…
It'll be okay.
I have a job, remember?
-I'll just go change.
-Patricia.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yes, Dad.
I just need some rest.
Diana, did you get any sleep?
-You need to rest.
-I'm fine.
I'm fine.
I bet you're thinking about what happened
to Patricia again, aren't you?
It can't happen again.
What's your plan?
She needs to get back on the right path.
She needs to go back to school.
I can't rely on Martin.
They're taking advantage of my daughter.
There's nothing we can do to stop you.
You are a mother, after all.
But, Diana, think about it,
Patricia is no longer a kid.
I'm just worried about her.
All you do is think about everyone, Diana.
It's always about Patricia, the company,
the employees, and the clients.
Try putting yourself first sometimes.
Who else should I think about, Nanny Cora?
Oh, Diana. You're not getting any younger.
You will be retiring in a few years.
What would your life be like then?
Have you ever thought
of spending your life with someone?
A partner who'll take care of you.
Oh, please, I gave up on that
a long time ago.
I don't think I can trust someone again.
Not all men are like Martin, you know.
Do you know any sensible man? Hmm?
A decent man who's successful, smart,
and will not be intimidated by me.
Someone sensible, hmm…
and doesn't have vices.
Someone who isn't a menace to society.
Hmm…
Someone who has a sound mind
and… kind.
She really thought
we couldn't afford bail, huh?
I'm really sorry for what happened.
Patricia definitely overreacted.
I thought she really needed the money.
Make sure she doesn't
get a job ever again.
Oh, I'll guarantee you that.
She wasted her big break.
She crashed and burned
before anyone even knew her.
But what happens to our case now?
Don't worry.
I have dirt on her.
I still have the video we took of her.
All in.
Let's see if she'd still press charges.
It'd be her honor on the line.
Seems you're lucky.
-Yes!
-Good game.
Uh, do you need anything?
Ah, yes.
All of Patricia's
audition footage is in there.
You've nothing to worry
about the producer and director.
Why are you doing this?
Part of my job
is to look after your image.
It's my job to care.
And also because…
Patricia doesn't deserve all that.
But how did you get this?
Diana, nothing is impossible.
Sometimes, we just have
to talk things out.
What do you need from us?
Where's Patricia's footage?
We don't have it!
-Agh!
-Please stop! Stop!
Give it to me.
Where is it? Give it to me.
Fine, I'll give it to you!
I'll give it to you, just please stop!
Please!
That wasn't so hard, was it?
We shouldn't have gone this far.
I'll get going.
Thank you for this.
And for protecting Patricia.
I appreciate it.
Is this you plan?
To be the next Mr. Aragon.
I thought you were the head of PR.
I wasn't aware…
that you're an aspiring gigolo
and a gold digger on the side.
Whatever you're doing,
it won't work on Diana.
Martin already tried that.
He gained her trust
and made her fall in love.
But then what happened?
She's too smart for antics.
-Interesting.
-It's very, very interesting.
And if you do get her,
and she allows you into her life,
I doubt it'll last long.
My sister doesn't know how to love.
She will get tired of you.
All she's capable of loving
are La Familia and…
herself.
You're right.
Diana loves La Familia more than her life.
What do you think
would she do to anyone who threatens it?
Knowing Diana,
she spares no one
when it comes to the company.
Not her family…
Not even her brother.
I read the pitch for Burger City.
As the marketing head…
I need a complete sentiment analysis
after the poisoning incident.
Are you trying to boss me around?
Have it ready by the end of the day, okay?
What's this?
Schools with evening classes.
With flexible schedules.
So you can study while still working here.
Why are you giving me this?
Ms. D asked me to.
Is it because of
what happened the other day?
Enzo, I won't give up on my dreams.
But Ms. D has a point, Patricia.
You almost got abused.
Perhaps it's time
to look at your other options.
But you know what…
not everyone is as bad as that director.
I still believe there are good people
who will give me a chance.
Don't take Ms. D's words the wrong way.
She's trying to give you
a chance at a better life.
If I do want to go back to school…
I will be the one deciding when and how.
Not because it's what she wants.
And most especially not
because I owe her anything.
Is that how you really view
this situation?
She can keep ordering me around
in this company.
She can ask me to do everything!
But only during my work hours here.
Outside of this building…
I'm in control of my life.
I get to decide…
what I want for myself,
what I can give up.
None of you can tell me
what I should give up.
Ma'am, even just
a five-minute appointment is fine.
Promise, that's all we need
for the elevator pitch.
I'm sorry, but the board's
schedule is packed.
And the board has no more interest
to continue further with La Familia.
Ma'am, what if we just talk to Mr. Smith?
We're under strict rules not to entertain
any more proposals. I'm really sorry.
Besides, Mr. Smith's not available today.
Why? Has he left the country?
We're not allowed
to disclose that information.
Patricia, this is over.
-We need to report to Ms. D.
-Huh? Wait, wait.
What, we're giving up just like that?
Want me to sneak inside?
I'll find Mr. Smith.
Patricia. Don't make a scene here.
Fine!
I'll just go pee.
-Fine. Make it quick.
-Yes.
Uh, ma'am, can I use the restroom?
-It's over there, ma'am.
-All right, thank you!
Hello? Hi, hon!
Yes, yes.
Ah, I'm here. I'm here downstairs.
I'll meet you at the parking lot.
I'm excited. I can't wait
for this vacation,
even if it's just one night!
I hear that Golden Sun Resort
is one of the best!
Yes. I'll see you.
I'll see you, hon. Okay!
What is it, Patricia?
Hey, hey! Where are you going?
I'm not going to give up.
Patricia, Mr. Smith's gone.
But that doesn't mean I'm out of options.
If a door closes on you,
then go through the window.
Ah, Enzo.
Enzo, updates, please,
on what I asked you to do.
Ms. D, Mr. Smith's already on vacation.
Oh, my!
Patricia, where are you going?
I know where Mr. Smith is.
I'll go and talk to him!
No, no, no. You can't do that.
Didn't you say
I should stop making excuses?
This is me finding a way.
But not this way! You cannot do that.
-You cannot.
-Why not?
That's not how we do things in business!
That's very unprofessional.
If you don't agree with what I'll do,
then let me do it myself.
No, no, no. Patricia.
Patricia!
Pat--
-Call Benjie right now.
-Yes, Ms. D.
Mr. Smith is not inside their room.
Well, they're on vacation.
I guess they went out.
-So--
-I'll look for them.
-How? Where?
-Uh-- Ms. D.
Diana!
Ms. Aragon! What are you doing here?
Um, if only we could have
a minute of your time.
-For what?
-Ple--
My company has already made
-its decision.
-We understand,
but we went out of our way
-to meet you here.
-This is inappropriate!
For you to come in here
like this unannounced,
and ruined, frankly, my time off?
We know, we're sorry, but just one--
My company cannot work with La Familia!
No means no!
We did what you wanted. Let's go home.
-But--
-Enough!
I've been humiliated enough!
We're going home.
What's so funny?
Uh…
There's no denying
that she is your daughter.
You're both stubborn.
Just get in the car.
Ma'am! Ma'am, are you okay?
I need my medicine. I'm a diabetic.
-Where is it? All right.
-In the car.
What-- What's happening?
-What's wrong?
-She's dizzy.
She needs to take her medicine. Wait.
-Oh!
-Oh, my goodness.
Is there anything else you need, ma'am?
I just need my medicine, please!
-Where is it?
-At the back. White bag.
Do you need water?
Should I call anybody?
-I think my husband
-Ms. D?
-is somewhere here.
-I see.
-So you're not driving? Okay.
-No, I can't.
-No, no. I just need to rest.
-Okay.
Hon?
What's happening here?
Honey, they helped me.
We need to take her to the clinic.
Thank you for helping me.
No, don't mention it.
Okay.
I've been giving this some more thought.
I don't like to see all the effort
that you've put into coming here wasted.
So, I'm giving you that chance to speak.
Why are you so insistent
on pursuing this deal?
Because this isn't just
another sales contract.
This is going to change
the entire trajectory
of both La Familia and Burger City.
Opportunities like this
don't just come around,
Mr. Smith.
Um, sir, if I may?
Ms. D?
The earliest memory I have…
of my mother…
is tied to Burger City.
When I was six years old…
my family and I went on a vacation abroad.
We ate at a Burger City there.
For a few days, I…
…I got something
I rarely had when I was growing up.
She wasn't a boss.
She wasn't an executive.
She was just my mother.
That's why, for me…
La Familia and Burger City
are always tied together.
Because they will always remind me…
of my time with my mother.
We both celebrate families
and connections.
It's safe to say that
we are the perfect pair.
Look, I'll bring this up
with our other board members
at the next management meeting.
I cannot promise you anything.
I think we must go.
Thank you very much, Mr. Smith.
Please think about it.
-I will.
-Thank you.
-Thank you again.
-Take care, ma'am. Thank you.
Wow, good job.
Great story.
Is it true?
Oh, I just made up some parts.
Don't forget, I'm an actor.
What is it?
Thank you.
You're welcome, Ms. D.
I made you proud, Dad.
It's like the universe was on our side.
We've been trying to convince
this foreign investor
from Burger City.
At first, he didn't even
want to talk to us.
Then Mr. Smith's wife
had a diabetic emergency.
So we helped her.
Mr. Smith appreciated what we did.
He gave us a chance
to present our proposal.
It looks like you're enjoying your job.
Not really.
I'm just glad I did something right.
You know, Patricia…
you don't have to impress your mother.
You won't be working
at La Familia for long.
-Dad?
-Hmm?
Why did you and Mom separate?
Huh?
Where did that come from?
You already know why.
I know you two
fought a lot when I was a kid,
but you never separated.
What made you decide to end your marriage?
Why are you asking me that?
I'm trying to remember if…
there was ever a time
when our family was happy.
Because all I remember is the pain.
That pain you remember…
was because of your mother.
Remember,
she abandoned us.
I don't want you to go through that again.
-You called for me?
-Mm-hmm.
We've heard from Burger City.
Ms. D wants you to be here
when she reads the email.
Okay, Enzo. Show us.
Let me read it.
"Dear Ms. Diana Aragon,
your passion and commitment are evident,
and we truly appreciate
the effort you've invested
in presenting this
partnership opportunity.
After careful consideration,
we are pleased to explore
this partnership further.
We believe there are a few final points
that will still require our mutual review,
but we are fully open to discussions
to finalize the details.
We look forward to building
a successful collaboration
with La Familia Beverages Corporation.
Sincerely, Jonathan Smith,
President and CEO
of Burger City Foods Inc."
Yes!
-Yes!
-Congratulations, everyone.
-Congrats to us.
-We did it!
Congratulations.
Great job.
The meeting with Burger City went great.
This is our second chance,
so let's not waste it.
This time, I want everything done right.
Teddy, prepare the marketing
strategies immediately.
We'll set another meeting for that.
Patricia, you help
with initial market research.
Enzo, legal. Coordinate with them.
I want to see the first draft
of the contract
on my table this afternoon.
Already on it, Ms. D.
What is the state
of the company's finances?
Will we be able to support
Burger City's future plans?
We can support the expansion, Ms. D.
But not without adjustments.
The food poisoning issue
heavily affected the sales of Cala Soda.
Right now, we are still
recovering our losses
while maintaining operating costs.
If we want to accommodate
the future demands of Burger City,
the company needs
to generate additional revenue
or reduce expenses.
Or we can lay off some employees, right?
The company has too many employees.
So, if we lay off some of them,
we'll definitely reduce our expenses.
Don't you agree?
I agree.
However, we can't sacrifice our employees.
This building is costing us
more than it should.
We are going to sell this building.
We'll relocate to the former
headquarters of La Familia.
If we do that,
we will greatly reduce our expenses.
Besides,
I think it's time we brought
La Familia back home.
Dismissed.
Did you get all the files from marketing?
-Pull out everything.
-Where should I put this, sir?
Please put it in Ms. D's office.
Thank you.
Everyone, everyone, listen!
We need to sort everything out, okay?
After Ms. D's meeting,
she's going to head here. Understood?
-Yes, sir.
-Thank you.
My gosh!
You're still here?
Yes. Are you going home?
This early? That's unlike you.
One of those rare moments.
You're taking work home?
I wouldn't be able to sleep anyway.
What's that?
This is what I take when I can't sleep.
You know, this needs to rest too.
It's hard to be alone.
The worst part is when you're
already lying in bed…
but you can't sleep
because you have a lot on your mind.
All your problems…
everything you’re going through,
so many regrets.
Take it so you can rest.
Thank you?
So--
Oh!
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Rest well, Ms. Aragon.
Good night.
-Okay.
-Thank you again, Mr. Smith.
-Thanks for coming by.
-Thank you so much.
I look forward to our next meeting.
As do I. Thank you.
-Okay.
-Mm-hmm.
Ms. D.
We have a lot to prepare
for La Familia's partnership
with Burger City.
So you need to clear out
a quarter of our office
because they're going
to need offices inside La Familia.
The partnership will push through?
Yes. We don't have any problems anymore
because everything has been cleared
and they value our competence
more than the rumors.
So get to work.
Make sure everything is prepared.
Yes, Ms. D.
Yes!
Wait.
Thank you.
Patricia helped me out in this, Ms. D.
All the years you've spent
training under me
didn't go to waste.
You've made me so proud, Enzo.
Thank you, Ms. D.
You can go.
You've been smiling since earlier.
See? You're still smiling.
I'm just happy.
Because Ms. D complimented you?
Well, I can't relate to that.
Huh?
She thanked you, too.
Come on, she appreciates you.
I remember when I was a kid…
all I heard from her was…
What?
-"Patricia, don't."
-What?
-"Patricia, stop doing that!"
-Huh?
"Patricia, you're so stubborn!"
Those things.
What?
Why? It's true, isn't it? You're stubborn.
Besides, aren't all mothers like that?
Well, yes, but…
Have I never done anything right?
Hmm?
Did you know…
when I was a kid, after my parents died,
I lived with my aunt.
But my aunt was young,
so she wasn't home most of the time.
She had to work.
So the people in La Familia…
became my guardians.
All the people my mom and dad worked with…
They took turns bringing me
to and from school.
Some of them even gave me an allowance.
And Ms. D?
Ms. D was always present
during my school activities.
She was the one who accompanied me
during my graduation.
It's impossible for me to relate to that.
I'm sorry.
He also had a huge debt before.
I knew it.
He's after Diana's money.
That's why he's trying
to get close to her.
Great.
Let's see if he can still
get close to her…
now that I have a card
to play against him.
I don't think anyone wins
in your betting game.
-You'll be the first one.
-Eat up.
-Oh, Patricia.
Oliver.
-Come.
-Uh, Dad.
Good thing you're home.
Why? What's going on?
It's your mother.
She wanted to treat us.
Go inside. You should eat.
Oliver, go inside.
Mm…
Dig in. There's a lot of food.
-It's so good!
-Sis, join us! It's good!
Hmm…
That food looks good, bestie.
Mom.
What's the occasion?
Just a little celebration
because I finally got a job.
Really, Mom?
Yes.
Where did you get the money to buy these?
I took a portion of our rent.
But don't worry.
Once I get my first salary,
I'll pay it back double.
What job is it? Where's your office?
Uh, I'll be a company secretary.
But I'm still taking care
of the requirements.
Don't worry. I'll tell you soon.
There's a surprise element, huh?
Mm-hmm.
Sis, sit down. Let's eat.
-Come on. It's good!
-Bestie, sit over there.
Mm.
I want a complete audit
of the PR Department.
All expenses, reimbursements.
All transactions.
Sir, that would need Ms. D's approval.
What approval are you talking about?
PR is under Marketing.
Am I not allowed to know
what's happening in my own department?
Just do it.
I have my suspicions about Ricardo.
He's riddled with debt.
All right.
I want everything confidential for now.
I'll take care of Diana.
Yes, I'm coming.
I'm sorry. I only had time just now.
Yes, I have the payment.
I'll give it to you, all right?
Isabelle Chavez…
Why are you following me?
Uh, Diana? You wanted to talk to me?
Explain yourself.
How will we trust people like that?
Think about it.
What if the people you're involved with
suddenly cause trouble here?
We don't deal with these kinds of people.
Is it true?
Yes.
But that's outside of my job
here at La Familia.
Oh, no.
The company policy has a morality clause.
Diana, that happened
before I was even employed here.
I am not stealing from your company.
Well, should we wait
for something to happen?
People addicted to gambling are dangerous.
They spare nothing and no one,
especially when they're desperate.
I am not doing anything wrong.
But Teddy's right.
This is too much of a liability.
Now, you're vulnerable
to blackmail, bribery, whatever.
And your contract has a morality clause.
Sir Ricardo, tell them the truth.
Patricia.
Patricia, this has nothing to do with you.
Of course. Fine, team up.
You're judging him for a mistake
he made in the past.
Yes, he has debts.
Yes, he gambled.
But he only did all that…
so he could pay
for his daughter's cancer treatment.
Patricia.
Sorry, Sir Ricardo.
They have to know.
You don't know what it feels like
to be desperate
just to save the person you love.
Why should this define him as a person?
He did so much for the company,
yet you do this to him?
Oh, my god. What is this?
Diana, what is this? I can't believe--
What kind of emotional
manipulation is this?
Is Patricia telling the truth?
Uh, yes.
Oh, my god, Diana…
Teddy…
How did you get these pictures?
Did you have someone spy
on one of the company's executives?
Teddy?
I was…
trying…
to think of the company.
All of you, get out of my office.
Are you going home?
Why didn't you tell me
about your daughter?
I will never exploit my daughter's memory
to defend myself.
I refuse to run away from my obligation.
Every debt must be paid.
I don't expect you to understand.
To do something wrong
just to save your child?
I understand.
Make sure this doesn't affect your job.
Aren't you going to fire me?
Don't give me a reason to fire you.
So it all backfired on you?
In the end, he became the victim.
All because Patricia came to his rescue.
He'll get what's coming to him someday.
Hey! Are you blind?
Sir, someone wanted you to have this.
Patricia, I assume
the office floor is ready
for the Burger City transition team?
They'll only be here temporarily,
but they'll serve
as our communication channel.
So all concerns, requests,
and coordination
must go through them.
Understood. All good, sir.
Okay. I think Mr. Borja
and his team are arriving soon.
Okay.
Good afternoon, Mr. Borja.
-Good afternoon.
-This is Patricia.
-Oh, it's nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you as well.
We can now proceed to your office floor.
So is everything ready
for our event tonight?
Yes, Patricia and I
double checked everything.
Perfect. Let's go.
Okay, let me escort you to your office.
-All right.
-Welcome.
Hello!
Surprise!
Mom…
What are you doing here?
Didn't I tell you I've got a new job?
This is it!
I'm back in the corporate world.
I've been assigned as the secretary
of Burger City's transition team.
Look at this.
So you have prior experience
working as a secretary?
Since I already worked at La Familia,
I know everything that needs to be done
as an executive secretary.
But that was years ago.
Um…
By the way, my daughter,
Patricia, works there.
If I may, Mr. Smith.
Um…
I've heard a lot of good things about you.
From whom?
Patricia Aragon, my daughter.
Isn't she the daughter
of La Familia's CEO?
She's the one who saved your wife.
Yes, that Patricia!
She considers me her mom
because I raised her
since she was very young
and taught her everything
she needs to know.
If she's Diana Aragon's daughter…
why don't you just ask for help
from your daughter
so you can get back to La Familia?
I don't want to use my daughter
to get a job.
I don't do that, sir, because…
of course, I'm protecting my daughter.
Just like a good mother should.
You raised a good daughter.
I know, right, sir?
Come on, Patricia. Don't you trust me?
Oh, no. It's not like that.
I'm just surprised.
Anyway, let's talk later.
Where's our office?
It's this way.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
-Mr. Smith.
-Ms. Aragon.
It's finally happening.
Ms. Aragon, this is wonderful.
Dear Patricia.
-Remember my daughter?
-I do, indeed.
-Thank you again.
-Nice to see you again, sir.
Sir, please make yourselves at home.
-Thank you.
-This is your table.
Hello. Welcome. Please.
You attend to Mr. Smith.
Yes, Ms. D.
Diana.
Hi. I'm sorry, I'm late.
I just escorted our media partners here.
I also brought in more content creators
to cover the event.
Oh, good.
Carlota, what are you doing here?
Uh…
You haven't told her yet, Patricia?
I'm one of the secretaries
working for Burger City.
What's the catch, Carlota?
I know you're planning something.
Aw, Ms. D…
Don't be so suspicious.
We're all professionals here.
Let's try to work together.
We don't really have a choice.
Whether we like it or not…
we're going to be working together.
I can handle it.
Can you?
You're right.
This is professional.
So I expect you won't cause any trouble.
Of course.
Mr. Borja!
-Hi, Mr. Smith.
-Oh, hi.
Ms. D…
Why didn't you tell me about Carlota?
I'm sorry. I got busy.
I only found out
she'd be working for Burger City earlier.
She's been looking
for a job for a long time
so she could help around the house.
Come on.
You know Carlota and I
aren't on good terms.
Not really, to be honest.
What exactly happened between you and Mom?
Why do you despise each other so much?
Didn't she and Dad get together
only after you two separated?
Is that what they told you?
We don't really talk about it at home.
That's all I know.
Patricia.
Dad?
Dad.
Martin!
I've been waiting for you.
Traffic was bad.
Are you sure I'm allowed to be here?
Of course.
I already got my boss's permission.
There are so many
potential business partners here.
Look.
Don't look at them.
Just relax before you go onstage.
And now, to kick off our launch,
let's hear some words
from the unbeatable, the unsinkable
Diana Aragon!
Thank you.
Dear friends, esteemed executives,
shareholders, and family,
a pleasant evening to all of you.
We have faced many challenges
these past months.
But as they say,
you cannot put good people down.
As we open this new chapter today
with Burger City,
who placed their trust in us
even through the storm,
we're sincerely grateful
for your trust and confidence.
And so, as we move forward
with this new partnership,
we are proud to present to you…
the vision of this partnership.
Stop! Stop-- Stop.
Stop this video! Stop this video!
Stop it!
Ms. D!
Patricia… Patricia, leave!
Go! Go. Leave.
-Ricardo, go with Patricia.
-Let's go.
I'm okay.
Go. Go!
Wait.
No.
Patricia…
Yes, I'm the girl in the video.
But that's not the whole truth.
What really happened…
was my director fooled me.
He told me…
that it was for an indie film,
but that was a lie.
They took advantage of me.
But nothing bad happened.
I was saved by Enzo and Ms. D.
I have nothing to be ashamed of.
I fought back,
unlike what the video
tried to make it seem.
The victim should not
suffer embarrassment!
Who should be embarrassed are the creator…
and the person
who showed it to the public.
I will not let myself…
be ruined by this video!
Because I will never accept
and I will never let myself…
be a mere victim in your eyes!
Patricia.
Let's go.
Patricia?
I'm not going back there.
Hey, hey…
It's okay.
Patricia…
Hey…
Look, I'm not letting you
go back there, okay?
Yes. Okay? I'm here.
Okay? It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
I'm here.
Breathe, breathe.
It's okay.
It's okay, Patricia.
Breathe.
It's okay.
Are you really that desperate for fame
-that you'd do that?
-Hey.
She's a victim.
Why didn't you tell Martin about this?
You can't protect our daughter.
Her life's been a mess since she got here!
Dad, that's enough.
This is an attack against me.
Why would they drag my daughter into this?
I hope Aunt Diana never let you in here.
You will never amount to anything.
Between the two of us, I am more worthy.
That's the flash drive I brought in, sir.
Then, where did that video come from?
I don't want to go to jail, Daddy!
-No…
-You won't go to jail.
They won't be able to prove it.
I was paid to do it.
But my conscience is eating away at me.
Who told you to do it? Tell me!
It's him.
I'm giving you a chance
to take control of your life.
It's so easy for you to give up on me.
Well, you never defended me, anyway.
A lot of people are waiting
for my downfall.
And they'd drag you down with me.
I'm protecting you.